Charles Bukowski papers, 1958-1988
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series III: Magazine Appearances, 1966-1977
  - The New York Quarterly, #21, pp. 29-30, 32-33: "Now She Hates Me," "That Chinaman Did Right?," "I Can Hear the Sound of Human Lives Being Ripped to Pieces" and I Paid $3.00 to See Bukowski Read." 1978 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Nitty-Gritty, v.1, #1: "86'd" broadside insert and Poems Written Before Jumping Out Of An 8 Story Window, review, author unknown. 1975 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Nomad, #5-6, Winter-Spring, pp. 5-6: "So Much for the Knivers, so Much for the Bellowing Dawns," "Manifesto: a Call for Our Own Critics" and ("the Day It Rained at the Los Angeles County Museum" which is listed in the index but missing from this defective copy.) 1960 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Notes From Underground, #3, p. 7: "Should We Burn Uncle Sam's Ass?" No Date (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Notes From Underground, #11, pp. 47, 66: "A Nice Place" and "All the White Rats." 1966 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Northwest Review, v.6, #2, Fall, p. 20: "A Drawer of Fish." 1963 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Northwest Review, v.6, #4, Fall, pp. 121, 123: "Breakthrough" and "Charles Bukowski and the Savage Surfaces" by John William Corrington. 1963 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Northwest Review, v.13, #1, p. 19: "59 Cents a Pound." 1978 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - The Ohio Review, v.14, #2, Winter, pp. 62-63: "little poem" and "Crime and Punishment." 1973 (Box 15, Folder 4a)
  - Offprints of the Above. 1973 (Box 15, Folder 4b)
  - Ole, v.1, #1 (#1), November: "watchdog," "freedom" and "age." 1964 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Ole, #3, November: "Drunk Again and Wondering, Wondering..." and notices of C.B. publications. 1965 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Ole, #4, May: "O, We Are the Outcasts, O We Burn in Wonderous Flame!" 1966? (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Ole, #5: "The Old Pro" an introduction to the poetry of Harold Norse (this issue is devoted to the poetry of Norse). 1966? (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Ole, #6, July: "Nature Poem" and "The Noiseless Car of a Blue Violet." 1966 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Ole, #7, May: reviews by C.B., The Anatomy of Love and Other Poems by John William Corrington, A Test of Poetry by Louis Zukofsky, Change of Address and Other Poems by Kathleen Fraser, and Empty Mirror by Allen Ginsberg. 1967 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Ole, #8, April: "Love Makes Its Gun into the Horrible Cut on Life." 1967 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Ole Anthology: "Freedom", "age" and "O We Are the Outcasts, O We Burn in Wonderous Flame" (this is a presentation copy to C.B. signed by the editor Douglas Blazek). 1967 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Open Skull, #1, pp. 11-12: letter from Alan Bleven to C.B. and letter from Al Purdy to C.B. 1967 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Out of Sight, #90(?): "Mine." No Date (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Outcry, #1: "Room Service." 1962 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - P-A-N, Summer, p. 10: "I need and I demand." 1977 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - The Painted Bride Quarterly, v.2, #4, Fall, pp. 14, 16: "mean and stingy" and "Nava, and life." 1975 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Paris Match #1532, October 6, p. 48: "A Bout Portant...Charles Bukowski" author unknown. 1978 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Pearl, #3, Spring-Summer, pp. 50-51: "the big ride" and "tables." 1978 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Pebble, #9, Winter: "A Day at the Oak Tree Meet" and "Coffee and Babies." 1972 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Pebble, #12, Winter: "Piss and Shit" and "Paper Clips." 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Playboy Deutschland, #12, December, p. 71: "Playboy Interview: Charles Bukowski." 1977 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Playboy Deutschland, July (?), p. 95: "Das passiert nur mis." 1978(?) (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Phoo: "Moyamensing Prison." 1969 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Poetry Newsletter, #7, February-March: Confessions of a Man Insane Enough to Live with Beasts, review author unknown. 1966 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Poetry Now, v. 1, #2 (#2), p. 24: "Cooperation." 1974 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Poetry Now, v.1, #3 (#3), p. 24: "The Man She Saw at the Racetrack." 1974 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Poetry Now, v.1, #5 (#5), p. 25: "Hooked." 1974 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Poetry Now, v. 1, #6, (#6), pp. 2-3: "2 horsecollars," "The First Love," "Your Own Toilet," "The Strangest Sight You Ever Did See--" and "Charles Bukowski." 1974 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Poetry Now, v.2, #1 (#7), p. 30: "The Red Porsche." 1975 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Poetry Now, v.2, #2 (#8), p. 27: "The Proud Thin Dying." 1975 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Poetry Now, v.2, #4 (#10), p. 16: "The Voice of the Bukowski." 1975 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Poetry Now, v.3, #1 (#13), p. 41: "This One Poet." 1976 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Prism International, v.6, #3, Spring, p.44: "The Seminar." 1976 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Pulse, #4, Summer/Fall: "cancer of the eyeball," "The Grammar of Life," "a need for glue" and letter from C.B. to Norm Moser (editor). 1971 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Purr, #1: "Bluebird" and "(a poem written in a letter to Linda King, Feb. 29, 1971...still pertinent...1975)." 1975 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Purr, #2: "my lucky friend," "It Works Like Liquid Snot coming out of Fire Hoses" and two full page drawings by C.B. 1975 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Pure Smutte, #1, November: "the sea walked in and out," "on the sidewalks and in the sun" and "the lady excecutives." 1972 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Quarry, #3, p. 31: "wide and revolving." 1973 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Quicksilver, v. 14, #3, Autumn, p. 18: "Vegas." 1961 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Quixote (Madison, Wisconsin), v.4, #9, p. 157: Poems Written Before Jumping Our of an 8 Story Window, review, author unknown. No Date (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Quixote (New York/Great Britain), #19, p. 27: "Hell Yes, the Hydrogen Bomb." 1958 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Rama, v.4, #1, p. 73: "Notes of a Dirty Old Man." 1974 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Renaissance, v.1 #1, July, p. 73: "the way to review a play and keep everybody happy but me." 1961 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Renaissance, v.1, #4, p. 96: "peace, baby, is hard sell" and letter from C.B. to John Bryan. 1962 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Rogner's Magazin, #9, September, pp. 69, 74, 198: Women (excerpt), "Bukowski" by Jörg Fauser with photos by M. Montfort, ad for Romane Und Stories with photo, and cover painting of C.B. 1977 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - rongWrong, #4, p. 1: "Something in Me Wants to Sing and Scream All Day Long." No Date (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - The San Francisco Book Review, #22, June, p. 24-27: " THE FLOWER LOVE," "Notes on the Life of an Aged Poet," "Love and Fame and Death" and "I Met a Genius." 1972 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - The San Francisco Quarterly, v.6, #1, Winter: "Charles Bukowski is the Top Dog" by Tony Qualiano. 1970 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Schist, #1, Fall, p. 7, 9: "These Little Talks in Room #109 with This Guy Called Harry" and a drawing. 1973 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Schist, #2, Summer, p. 52: "The New One." 1974 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Schist, #3, Spring, p. 24: "problems about the other woman" and "a class broad." 1975 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Sciamachy, #5, pp. 9-10: "Existence" and "Notice." 1963 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Scree, #5, pp. 35-37: "alone with everybody," "milk a cow and get milk," "the insane always loved me" and "the meaning." 1976 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Scree, #7, pp. 14-15, 20: "theis then--," "a killer," "sex" and a drawing. 1976 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Second Aeon, #13, pp. 77-79: "slim killer," "poem for Dante" and "the conditions." 1971? (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Second Aeon, #14: "burning." No Date (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Second Aeon, #16/17, pp. 53, 57: "assault" and "a poorly night." No Date (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Scond Coming, v.1, #2, Summer: "Burning in Water, Drowning in Flame." 1972 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Second Coming, v.2, #3, (special C.B. issue). No Date (Box 17, Folder 8)
    "Six Inches"
    "He Beats His Women"
    "Love Poem to Marina"
    "Poem to a Man in Jail"
    "Layover"
    "The Knifer"
    "Beerbottle"
    "Don't Come Around But If You do..."
    Letters
    Articles/Poems/Letter by Steve Richmond, Neeli Cherry, George Tsongas, Jerry Kamstra, Jack Micheline, Harold Norse, Guy Williams, Ann Menebroker, Alta, Gerald Locklin, G.J. Melling, Linda King, and Hugh Fox.
  - Second Coming, v.2, #4/5, Summer, p. 34: "In the Name of Love and Art." 1973 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Second Coming, v.5, #1: Special C.B., A.D. Winans, Ed "Foots" Lipman issue. 1977 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    "The Crunch"
    "Through and Through"
    "Goodbye, Goodbye, Clipped-winged Bluebird"
    "I'm as Crazy as I Ever Was"
    "Hunchback"
    "Be Alone"
    "Melancholia and the Redhead"
    "Carrot"
    "Poet and Poetess..."
    "The Poem of the Empty bed"
    "Weep"
    "Against the Tide:
    "Time"
    "light Brown"
    "The Promise"
    "Waving and Waving Goodbye"
    "The 6 Foot Goddess"
    "Beer"
    "How to Be a Great Writer"
    "Bedpans"
    "Carltton Way off of Western"
    ""462-0614"
    "For A.D."
    Photo of C.B.
  - The Serif, v.8, #4, December, p. 24: an untitled prose piece about d.a. levy and Jon Webb. 1971 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Shaded Room, #1, March, p. 41: Poems Written Before Jumping Out of an 8 Story Window review, author unknown. 1970 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - The Shore Review, #12/13, pp. 26, 28, 29, 30-31: "Moths," "The Drill," "Soul," "Did You ever Think about that?," and "The Experts." 1974 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Showcase, #2, November-December, pp. 6-7: "The High-rise of the New World" and "On the Train to Del Mar." 1965 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Showcase, #3, July: "Poem for My Daughter" and "Good Morning." 1966 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Signet, v.3, #12, December, pp. 9-10: "The Ants" and "Ringed Bathrub, Peacock or Hell." 1961 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Simbolica, #21: "Ample Sewers" and "Dialogue: Dead Man on a Fence." No Date (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Simbolica, #22, pp. 14-17: "Some Notes on Bach and Hayden" "6x9," "Till Eulenspiegal and Me," "Primer for Students of Love" and "The Powerful Way of Mystery Is L(k)e a Glad(io)la Bl(oo)***ing." No Date (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Silver, pp. 25, 29: "iron and stone: and "down on the row." 1972 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Sixpack, #2, August, pp. 53-54: Erections, Ejaculations, Exhibitions and General Tales of Ordinary Madness, review by Pierre Joris, and Mockingbird Wish Me Luck, review by R.M. 1972 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Small Press Review, v.4, #4 (#16), May, (special C.B. issue): "Upon the Mathematics of the Breath and the Way," "A Poem as a City," "Style," (these are quoted in separate articles), articles/poems about C.B. by Tony Qualiano, Sandy Dorbin, Harold Norse, William Packard, Linda King, Felix Pollack, Len Fulton, photos of C.B. and photo of Linda King's sculpture of C.B. 1973 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - some/thing, v.2, #1, Winter: "Drawing of a Band Concert on a Match Box." 1966 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Southern California Lit Scene, v.1, #1, December, pp. 30-31: "Looking for the Giants" an interview by William Robson and Josette Bryson and photos of C.B., cover. 1971 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Spectroscope, v.1, #1, April: "Essay on Nothing for Your Mother--Nothingness" and "The Devious good of Rescuing the Suffering." 1966 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Steppenwolf, #4, autumn, p. 31: "Quits." 1970 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Stern Magazin, February, p. 68: "Heissgeliebter Drecksack" by Wilhelm Bittorf. 1978 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Stonecloud, #2, pp. 19-20, 95: "a radio with guts," "Trouble with Spain" and "I can't see anything." 1973 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Stooge, #3: "shoelace," "my hell," "nothing for a title...," "o, yes" and "A Bottomless Joint on Sunset near Western." No Date (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Stump, #1: "One for Blaise Cendrars." 1973 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Summer Madness: "The Places a Poem Can Take You." No Date (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - The Sunset Palms Hotel, v.2, #4, Spring: cover and two other drawings by C.B. 1974 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - The Sunset Palms Hotel, v.4, #7, Winter: "Death." 1976 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - the, #13: "me" and "F.F. (for G. and C.)." No Date (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Throb, #1, Spring, pp. 2-5: "Bug," "Summer," "The Elements" and "Summer." 1971 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Throb, #2, Summer/Fall, p. 56: "Charles Bukowski Answers 10 Easy Questions." 1971 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Today, v.21, #7, April, p. 30: "Charles Bukowski: Outsider No. 1" by Jay Robert Nash with photos. 1966 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Twen, April, pp. 5, 60: "Der Tag, an dem wir über James Thurber sprachen" and biographical sketch with photos. 1971 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Underground Digest, v.1, #2, March, p.76: "Notes of a Dirty Old Man." 1967 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Unmuzzled Ox, v.1, November, pp. 16-17: "Poem" and "Tragedy Is My Bacon." 1971 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Unmuzzled Ox, v.1, #4, February, p. 42: "Goodyear." 1972 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Unmuzzled Ox, v.4, #2, Autumn: " "3:16 and One Half..." 1972 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Unmuzzled Ox, v.4, #2: "One for R.O." 1976 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Vagabond, v.1, #2, p. 23: "I will Never Ride a Horse along the Sands of Normandy or against the Sides of Your Brain, Lilac-raining Like It Is Tonight." 1966 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Vagabond: "The Flower Lover," "I Met a Genius" and notes with drawing of C.B. 1967 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Vagabond, #10, p. 3: "Fat upon the Land." 1971 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Vagabond, #11, p. 41: "The Shoelace." 1971 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Vagabond, #12, p. 16: "Dirge." 1971 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Vagabond, #13, pp. 21-22, 24: "A Man's Woman," "The Snake in the Watermelon" and "Work-fuck Problems." 1972 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Vagabond, #15, pp. 38, 40: ""99 degrees" and "The Oldest Hippie in the World." 1972 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Vagabond, #17, p. 12: "visit to Venice." 1973 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - The Willie, #1, Summer: "The Kiss-off" and "One Hundred and Ninetyseven Degrees." 1967 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - The Willie, #2, Spring: "bogart in the world of the dead." 1968 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Willmore City, #2/3, Fall, p. 8: "the good life." 1975 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Wormwood, #12, v.3, #4, pp. 19-20, 27: "It's not /who lived here/but who died here" (first lines), "Poem for My 43rd. Birthday," "The End" and "The Vulgar Sounds Rise My Misery." 1963 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Wormwood, #13, v.4, #1, p. 23: "The Hours." 1964 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Wormwood, #20, v.4, #4, pp. 16-18: "finish," "Female and Breakdown and Peace" and "6.21 P.M.." 1965 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Wormwood, #21, v.5, #1, pp. 23-25: "dear friend," "One Hundred and Ninetynine Pounds of Clay Leaning Forward" and "a world, really--." 1966 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Wormwood, #22, v.5, #2, pp. 6-7: "Note on a Bluebird Flying Past My Window," In This Place We Eat Apples and Cut Our Fingers on Beercans" and "anything." 1966 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Wormwood, #24, v.6, #4: Night's Work (centerfold chapbook with C.B. drawings). 1966 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    "Buffalo Bill"
    "a little atomic bomb"
    "The colored Birds"
    "Somebody always breaking my dainty solitude..."
    "fag, fag, fag"
    The Screw-Game"
    "a beginner's bibliography of bukowski" author unknown but probably Marvin Malone.
  - Wormwood, #27/28, v.7, #3/4, p. 20: quoted blurb. 1967 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Wormwood, #29, v.8, #2, pp. 21-22: "One for Ging, with Klux top" and "footnote upon the construction of the masses." 1968 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Wormwood, #30, v.8, #2, pp. 30, 35: "No Hole in the Sky," At the Hour of the Daily Reckoning" and "Bukowski" by Hugh Fox. 1968 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Wormwood, #31, v.8, #3, p. 34: "The Underground." 1968 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Wormwood, #33, v.9, #1, p. 13: "the ladies still don't care." 1969 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Wormwood, #39, v.10, #3, pp. 94-96: " A Correction to a Lady of Poetry," "A Warm Afternoon Just Off Sunset Boulevard," "yes," and "boil near left elbow." 1970 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Wormwood, #40, v.10, #4, pp. 150-151: "16 Jap Machinegun Bullets" and "When All the Animals Lie Down." 1970 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Wormwood, #41, v.11, #1, p. 33: "looking for Jack Micheline." 1971 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Wormwood, #42, v.11, #2, pp. 65-66: "the bombing of Berlin," "the great writer" and "Ice." 1971 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Wormwood, #43, v.11, #3, p. 117: "hey, hank." 1971 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Wormwood, #44, v.11, #4, pp. 132-134: "something on Berlioz," "the butvher" and "my landlady." 1971 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Wormwood, #45, v.12, #1, p. 3: "The Outsider" essay on Jon Edgar Webb. 1972 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Wormwood, #46, v.12, #2, p. 63: "The Smoking Car" and "Poetry, You Whore..." 1972 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Wormwood, #47. v/12. #3, pp. 103-104: "I met this woman," and "the painter." 1972 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Wormwood, #48, v. 12, #4, p. 135: "The Last Poetry Reading." 1972 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Wormwood, #49, v.13, #1. p. 38: "Daylight Saving" and "Born to Lose." 1973 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Wormwood, #50, v.13, #2, pp. 69-70: "The Angels Say Keep Going" and "Vacancy." 1973 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Wormwood, #51, v.13, #3, pp. 114-116: "our song," "my afternoons into night" and "Bukowski." 1973 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Wormwood, #53, v.14, #1: 55 Beds in the Same Direction (centerfold chapbook). 1964 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    "200 years"
    "finish"
    "55 beds in the same direction:
    "well, now that Ezra has died..."
    "tarot"
    "Eleven"
    "no bra, no panties"
    "a bit of light for the toad"
    "demise"
  - Wormwood, #55, v.14, #2, pp. 107-108: "girls coming home in their cars," 75 million dollars" and "some picnic." 1974 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Wormwood, #56, v.14, #4, p. 151: "Bukowski at His Best" by Gerald Locklin. 1974 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Wormwood, #57, v. 15, #1, pp. 38, 40-41: "Poor Trochi," "Fair Stand the Fields of France and Negation," "Round Trip--for T.H." and "There's People in Places Where Snow Lives." 1974 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Wormwood, #60, v.15, #4, pp. 117-119: ""Look for That Guy," "An Old Fan," "Shoot Me in the Leg, Shouts the Sky; Some Good Soul Does as the Sawdust Fall Through--" and "Kiss Me." 1975 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Wormwood, #62, v.16, #2, pp. 78-80: "Cloud 9," "I Like to Look up at the Ceiling/for Designs in the Cracks" and "Susan's Sunset and Western." 1976 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Wormwood, #64, v.16, #4, pp. 142-144: "Free," "Utah" and "Let's Be Original." 1976 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Wormwood, #65/66, v.17, #1/2, p. 44: "Blinks a Little Spot of Senseless Yellow in the Middle of It All." 1977 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Writers Forum, v.3, #4, Spring, p. 35: "Propoganda." 1967 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Yellow Brick Road, #4: "this one poet." 1975 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Uknown title, may be an issue of Runcible Spoon, August: "dooby do do do," "the shit shits," "shoot the goat through the head and paint the bones green" and "the vast area of space nothingness with snakes crawling through me and you and everything--." 1970 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Series IV: Miscellaneous Materials, 1966-1980
  Includes: Books, anthology, appearances, introductions, photos, broadsides, presentation copies, acrylic drawings by C.B., a critical study, statement of income, and racing forms. Additional oversized miscellaneous materials are continued in Series VI.
  - Poetas de Hoy en los Estados Unidos, edited by Miller Williams, Santiago, Chile, Ministerios de Educación, p. 116: "The Tragedy of the leaves," and "La Tragedia de las Hojas by Cinna Lomnitz. 1966 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Z: An Anthology of Revolutionary Poetry edited by Dan Georgakas, New York, Smyrna Press, p. 21: "The Tragedy of the Leaves" and "Ho Chi Minh." 1968 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Mad Windows, edited by Phill Perry, Notre Dame, Indiana, Lit Press, p. 40: "These Made Windows That Taste Life and Cut Me if I Go through Them." 1969 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Holy Doors: An Anthology of Poetry, Prose, and Criticism, edited by William J. Robson, Long Beach, California p102: letter from C.B. to William J. Robson and letters and commentary with various references to C.B. 1972 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - The Venice Poetry Company Presents, edited by Ted Simmons, Los Angeles, Venice Poetry Company Association, pp. 19, 39: "It's All in the Burning" and "the bombing of Berlin." 1972 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Anthology of L.A. Poets, edited by C.B., Neeli Cherry and Paul Vangelisti, Los Angeles, Laugh Literary/Red Hill Press: 1972 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    Includes: "A Forward to These Poems," "29 Chilled Grapes," "another academy," 'if we take--" and "style."
  - Invitation to a Dying, Al Maserik, Redwood City, California, Vagabond Press: "An Introduction to These Poems." 1972 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Contemporary Poetry n America, edtied by Miler Williams, New York, Random House, pp. 60-61. 1973 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    "The Human Condition"
    "The Tragedy of the Leaves"
    "The Singular Self"
    "footnote upon the construction of the masses"
    "For Jane"
  - Specimen 73: A Catalog of Poets for the Season, edited by Paul Vangelisti, Pasadena, California, Pasadena Museum of Modern Art. 1973 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    "The Priest and the Matador"
    "another academy"
    "Old Man Dead in a Room"
    "Law"
    "Love and Fame and Death"
    "if we take--"
  - Something Else yearbook, edtied by Jan Herman, West Glover, Vermont, Something Else Press Inc., p. 108: "A Poem to Myself." 1974 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Earth Rose, Steve Richmond, Santa Monica, California, Earth Books - presentation copy to C.B.: "Forward." 1974 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Intrepid Anthology: A Decade & Then Some, Contemporary Literature, edited by Allen De Loach, Buffalo, New York, Intrepid Presspp. 27-30: "Overtime," "The Girl Outside of Strawberry Patch # One," "Another One of My Critics" and "The Police Helicopter." 1976 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - California Bicentennial Poets Anthology, edited by A.D. Winans, San Francisco, Second Coming Press, pp. 17-20: "For Jane," "The Tragedy of the Leaves," "The Priest and the Matador," and "Something for the Touts, the Nuns, the Grocery Clerks and You..." 1976 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Hierophant, #1: presentation copy from the editor Tom Kerrigan. 1969 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - The Tibetan Stroboscope, d.a.levy, Cleveland, Ayizan Press: presentation copy from the author. 1968 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Notes of a Dirty Old Man, North Hollywood, Essex House. 1969 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - We'll Take Them, Santa Barbara, Black Sparrow Press, ( Sparrow 72, last of the series). 1978 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Dear Mr. Bukowski, San Luis Obispo, California, Garage Graphics, (44/50, signed). Text and drawings by C.B. Silkscreened by Ray Hartman onto 11 cards plus colophon, inserted into envelope with ribbon tie. 1979 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Kargo, Thomas Brasch, Frankfurt am Main, Suhrkamp Verlag: presentation copy from author. 1977 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Racing forms from Hollywood Park, each has been work out and signed. 1980 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Various miscellaneous items. No Date (Box 20, Folder 6)
    "An Answer to a Critic of Sorts", Phoenix(?), 1975(?), Broadside.
    Photos (nine) of C.B., two with unidentified friends, one with Linda King sculpture.
    Statement of income/expenses for tax purposes.
    A poem, a group of nine poems, a drawing by unidentified persons.
    Photos (three) of two unidentified women.
  - Charles Bukowski: Notes from the American Underground, Doub Pibel, probably a graduate paper. 1977 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Acyrlic drawings, two, both signed. No Date (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Series V: Foreign Language Publications, 1973-1979
  - Der Mann Mit Der Ledertasche (Post Office), translated by Hans Hermann, Köln, Verlag Kiepenheuer & Witsch. 1974 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Der Mann Mit Der Ledertasche, translated by Hans Hermann, München, Duetscher Taschenbuch Verlag. 1977 (Box 21, Folder 2)